Owen Mok

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER | WEB DEVELOPER

147 Charville Ln, Hayes UB4 8PB, UK •

mxnre.github.io



SUMMARY

Hello! This is Owen Mok, a fullstack and senior blockchain developer with over 7 years of experience. I love to write code in a high-paced and challenging environment with an emphasis on using best practices to develop high quality software that meets project requirements, budget, and schedule. I enjoy learning new technologies and sharing findings with my colleague.

- Always Open to Remote Job
- 6+ years of experience in Web Development

Experience in React/Redux development/Tawilwind CSS more than 5 years.

Composed front-end app structure & built React components and UI from given mockup.

Good TypeScript programming skills in VueJS and ReactJS.

Good knowledge of Functional Programing, Object-Oriented Programming and design patterns.

React | React Native | Redux | Vue | Angular | Node | Typescript | Next | Nuxt | MongoDB | Tailwind CSS | Storybook

- 3+ years of experience in Blockchain Development

Experience with Solidity, web3.js, ethers.js, Hardhat with a strong understanding of

Design, develop, program, test, debug, maintain smart contracts code.

Build governance systems with multi-stage voting.

Worked on many DeFi and Dapps based on Ethereum Blockchain and have enough experience in developing and writing Smart Contracts.

Expert in Uniswap, Sushiswap, Swapping tokens, Staking, Yield Farming, Lottery Smart Contracts etc.

Evaluate and evolve scalability, security, performance, and gas optimization.

Solidity | Ether.js | Web3.js | Rust | Hardhat

SKILLS

| REACT.JS | | SMART CONTRACT | |
|----------|---|----------------|------|
| VUE.JS | $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ | TRON | •••• |
| WEB3.JS | $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ | INFURA | •••• |
| ETHER.JS | • • • • • | TRUFFLE | •••• |
| SOLIDITY | • • • • • | HARDHAT | •••• |
| RUST | • • • • • | METAMAST | •••• |
| PYTHON | • • • • • | SOLANA | •••• |

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Grayblock Jan 2021 - Present

- Built a front-end application for minting and staking using React and Web3.js.
- Contributed to staking contracts with Solidity.
- Performed smart contract security audits.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Escrow Protocol Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

- Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and Web3.js.
- Contributed to a contract for NFT registration and redemption with Solidity.
- Created a POC Vue.js front-end platform for an NFT gallery using Moralis and Vue.
- Worked on the token distribution and migration from BSC to Polygon network using BscScan, PolygonScan API, and Solidity.

Technologies: DApps, Web 3.0, Solidity, Ethereum.

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Centrys, Inc *Jan 2019 - Jan 2020*

- Wrote smart contracts and fixed security holes.
- Contributed to one of the biggest mining pools on the AION network.
- Implemented an IBFT consensus algorithm for the AION Blockchain.
- Created a permissioned blockchain with the newly implemented consensus.
- Developed smart contracts for testing new blockchain features.

Technologies: C#, Encryption, AES, Blockchain, Solidity, Ethereum, Java

FULLSTACK ENGINEER

Holidu Feb 2016 - Dec 2018

- Composed front-end app structure & built React components and UI from given mockup.
- Integrated Redux and MobX on a number of React-based front-end projects for the better state management of React components.
- Implemented a GraphQL-and-Apollo server for a React-and-Vue.js front-end data query.
- Created a new customized chart library using D3.js and Plotly.js.
- Embedded a Google tag manager and Google Analytics for the website conversion tracking and the user event tracking.
- Integrated Vue.js, Vuex, and Vuetify with a Laravel back-end.

Technologies: AWS Lambda, GraphQL, Node.js, Vue.js, React, PHP, JavaScript

FRONTEND ENGINEER INTERN

Myxer Mar Feb 2016

- Developed a streaming music service front-end that allows users to create custom radio stations.
- Created and optimized AngularJS services, directives, bindings, and event handlers used for radio station user UX.
- Fixed several bugs and reworked the UI/UX to provide smoother interactions with a web app while music was streaming.

Technologies: Less, CSS, AngularJS, JavaScript

EDUCATION Bachelor's degree of Computer Science

Singapore Institute of Technology Apr 2010 - Oct 2014

LANGUAGES ENGLISH • • •